affiliateedge.com 2018-05-27

# Affiliate Edge - Privacy Statement

**Last updated May 23, 2018**

Affiliate Edge (“we” or “us” or “our”) respects the privacy of our users (“user” or “you”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit Affiliate Edge, including any other media form, media channel, mobile website, or mobile application related or connected thereto (collectively, the “Site”). Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT ACCESS THE SITE.

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. We will alert you about any changes by updating the “Revised” date of this Privacy Policy. Any changes or modifications will be effective immediately upon posting the updated Privacy Policy on the Site, and we will inform you of any updates via email.

## LAWFUL BASIS

Affiliate Edge has identified “Legitimate Interest” as the lawful basis for the processing of personal information. 

The legitimate interests pursued are; the prevention of fraud, contacting customers for security, support and account purposes, and for direct marketing to customers that have actively opted in to communication.

The data collected is only that which relates directly to the processing aims as stated above, and therefore this is a lawful basis for the processing of personal information.

## COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION

By signing up to and using the site, you consent to the following information being collected about you:

### Personal Data

We collect certain personal data about you directly; i.e. information that you provide by filling in forms on Affiliate Edge, such as when you register contact information or payment details.

Personally identifiable information collected may include (but is not limited to); your name, address, email address, telephone number and/or Skype username, payment details and demographic information, being your age, gender and hometown, that you provide us when you register with the Site.

You are under no obligation to provide us with personal information of any kind, however your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of Affiliate Edge.

All data provided to us is held on our secure servers.

### Derivative Data

In addition to information that you provide directly to use, in operating our website we may collect and process the following data about you:

  1. Details of your visits to our website and the resources that you access, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs, IP address, operating system, access times, what browser you are using and other communication data.
  2. Information provided to us when you communicate with us for any reason.

Once this data has been collected, we will store it on our secure servers.

### Financial Data

All monetary transactions are undertaken in line with our terms and conditions.

Where an external processor is used, processors will collect and store information related to the transaction. Each payment processor will have their own privacy policy outlining how they handle your personal information. You are encouraged to review their privacy policy and contact them directly with any questions you may have regarding this information. We do not collect or store any of this data ourselves.

## USE OF YOUR INFORMATION

Having accurate information about you permits us to provide you with a safe, smooth and efficient experience. Specifically, we use information collected about you to:

  * Create and manage your account.
  * Email you regarding your account activities.
  * Fulfill and manage payments, and other transactions.
  * Prevent fraudulent transactions, monitor against theft, and protect against criminal activity.
  * Request feedback and contact you (excluding marketing – see below).
  * Resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems. 
  * Notify you about any changes to our website, such as improvements or service/product changes that may affect our service
  * Personalise your experience
  * With your consent only, we deliver targeted marketing regarding our website and mobile application to you.

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may share information we have collected about you in certain situations. Your information may be disclosed as follows: 

### By Law or to Protect Rights

If we believe the release of information about you is necessary to respond to legal process, to investigate or remedy potential violations of our policies, or to protect the rights, property, and safety of others, we may share your information as permitted or required by any applicable law, rule, or regulation. This includes exchanging information with other entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Third-Party Service Providers

We may share your information with third parties that perform services for us or on our behalf, including payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service, and marketing assistance. We are committed to only working alongside third parties that comply with the General Data Protection Regulation and have taken all reasonable steps to confirm their compliance.

## TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, and other tracking technologies on Affiliate Edge to help customize and improve your experience. For more information on how we use cookies, please refer to our Cookie Policy posted on the Site, which is incorporated into this Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to be bound by our Cookie Policy.

## THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES

The Site may contain links to third-party websites and applications of interest, including advertisements and external services, that are not affiliated with us. Once you have used these links to leave the Affiliate Edge Site, any information you provide to these third parties is not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of your information. Before visiting and providing any information to any third-party websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of the third party responsible for that website, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect the privacy of your information. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other sites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Site.

## SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

We use administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your personal information. While we have taken all reasonable steps to secure the personal information you provide to us, please be aware that despite our efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable, and no method of data transmission can be 100% guaranteed against any interception or other type of misuse. Any information disclosed online is vulnerable to interception and misuse by unauthorized parties. If you have reason to be concerned that your personal data has been accessed in such a way, we request that you contact us as soon as possible using the contact information provided. We are committed to keeping your data safe; in the unlikely event that a data breach does occur we have full Data Breach reporting procedures in place which will be closely followed.

## POLICY FOR CHILDREN

We do not knowingly solicit information from or market to children under the age of 18. If you become aware of any data we have collected from children under age 18, please contact us using the contact information provided below.

## CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. No uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this Privacy Policy.

## OPTIONS REGARDING YOUR INFORMATION

### Requesting your own data

By logging into your account you are able to view the majority of your personal information that is stored on our system.

You also may at any time request a copy of the information about you that is held by ourselves. In order to request this information, you should use the contact information provided. Once a request is received we have one month to respond to you unless the request is particularly complex, in which case we will inform you of any delay within one month of the request being received.

### Account Information

You may at any time review or change the information in your account or terminate your account by:

  * Making adjustments in your account yourself
  * Contacting the Affiliate Team to make any changes to your account details.
  * To delete or deactivate an account, affiliates should contact the affiliate team using the contact information provided. Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our archived files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.

### Emails and Communications

If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from us, you may opt-out by:

  * Clicking on Unsubscribe links at the email footer, or;
  * Contacting us using the contact information provided.
  * If you no longer wish to receive correspondence, emails, or other communications from third parties, you are responsible for contacting the third party directly. 

### Data Breach and Incident reporting

Where a data breach is identified, an assessment of the potential impact of the breach is undertaken. Based on the result of this assessment, we will then notify the relevant supervisory authority and individual data subject(s) as required.

## CONTACT US

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#e28f838c8385879091a28384848b8e8b83968787868587cc818d8f)
